Friends, let's discuss in this video the results of
ICC Lombard. They have
recently announced the fourth quarter results
and they have
also given a declaration. Here
we are seeing a dividend of 5.5%,
which is the amount you will
get as dividend on the top share and this is also going to be its income, only then
we will know the record date in it. So let's
discuss its results. The company
's numbers are very impressive. If we
talk about total income, then
look here, we are
seeing growth for the previous year. As per the previous
quarter also,
we are seeing very good growth in this quarter. If we
talk about growth, then indirectly we are
seeing a growth of 15%. If we look at cotton cotton piece
also, then
we are seeing a jump of 20% here, so
we are seeing very good numbers here. If we
also talk about the profit of the company, then here
we will see a
lot here.  Good growth is being seen, sir,
we are seeing a growth of about 40%
and here
we are seeing very good growth in cotton,
which is a very good thing in itself
because this is a company from the insurance sector,
so here its
quarterly results have been announced and if we also look at the
NPA of the company, then we are seeing a
lot of improvement here, so
overall
if we look at it, we are seeing
very good results here,
now we will also talk about the technical chart, so
look here, exactly the
stock has reached the support level here, so there will be a high
possibility of
seeing an upward bounce from here
and friends, if you have
not yet opened a demat account in Angel One, then the
link is given in the description box, by using that
link you
can also open a demat account for free, so
friends, let's go to Angel One Up,
friends, we have come to Up,
after that in the list, type the name of the stock in the search box.  You have to
search and add it, we have already
added it, we will tap on it, the
interface will show something like this, simply
we have to touch buy,
after touching buy, if you want to buy and hold the stock
for overnight, then you will
type in delivery, if you want to sell, then
you will interact in delivery, here
we already have to enter, suppose
we need 25 quantity here, then
we will enter 25 quantity here below
and the market option is given, limited, you
can buy at your desired price, like
its current price is
1083.35, if you want to buy it
at 18, then you will enter it here, whenever
its price is here today, your order will be
executed, now what is the market rate,
market rate means whatever is its
running price,
your order gets executed directly on this,
simply we have to touch buy,
after touching buy, it will be confirmed,
after confirming, our order is  It will be
executed successfully, the process will be there
for internet also, so friends, this was all in today's
video, which has been
made only for educational purpose,
whenever you make it active in stock, then
make clay in it only after mixing it with your finish, so
let's meet in the next video
[Music]